Prentiss Taylor
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1885-1991, undated, Series 10:; (Box 3-21, OV 22; 18.0 linear feet; Reels 5913-5935)
  - Dorothy Adlow, 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 315-317)
  - Polly Aird, 1935? (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 319-322)
  - Grace Albee, 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 324-328)
  - Hardie Albright, undated (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 330)
  - John Alden, 1945-1954 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 332-362)
  - Nancy Jane Virginia Alderson, 1926-1956 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 364-374)
  - Elizabeth Alexander (Mrs. John White Alexander), 1929-1978, (7 folders) (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 376-703)
  - Alexandria Gazette, 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 705-706)
  - Alexandria Medical Society, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 708-709)
  - Charles H. Alldredge, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 711)
  - John D. Allen, undated (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 713)
  - Lester Allentuck, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 715)
  - Gordon K. Allison (H. V. Allison & Company), 1941-1973 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 717-724)
  - All Souls Unitarian Church, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 726-730)
  - Glen Alps, 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 732)
  - Harold Altman, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 734-735)
  - Ethel Altschul (Mrs. Syulvan Altschul), 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 737-738)
  - Daisy Alwine, 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 740-741)
  - Victor Amato, 1950-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 743-749)
  - Irving Amen (Amen Gallery), 1961-1970 (Box 3, Reel 5914, Frame 751-832)
  - American Artists Group, 1936-1953 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 835-862)
  - American Artists Professional League, Inc., undated (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 864)
  - American Council on Education, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 866-876)
  - American Federation of the Arts, 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 878-883)
  - American Institute of Architects, 1951-1974 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 885-895)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 897-899)
  - American Journal of Psychiatry, 1950-1961 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 901-948)
  - American Journal of Psychotherapy, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 950-953)
  - American National Committee of Engraving, 1941 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 955)
  - American Psychological Association, 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 957-966)
  - American University, 1950-1975, (4 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 968-1153)
  - Catharine McEwen Ames, 1956 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1155-1156)
  - Elizabeth Ames, undated (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1158)
  - John L. Ames, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1160-1164)
  - Anacostia Neighborhood Museum, Smithsonian Institution, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1166-1187)
  - Vera Andrus, 1949-1959 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1189-1201)
  - Cornelia Anker, 1954 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1203-1204)
  - Katharine Anthony, 1935-1965 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1206-1216)
  - Robert Anthony, 1956 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1218-1220)
  - John T. Appleby, 1974 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1222)
  - Anne Archbold, 1945-1957 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1224-1226)
  - Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution, 1970-1986 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1228-1252)
  - University of Arizona, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1254-1295)
  - Arlington County, Virginia, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1297-1298)
  - Arlington Towers Associates, 1955-1980 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1300-1366)
  - John Taylor Arms, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1368-1374)
  - John M. Armstrong, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1376-1387)
  - Susannah Armstrong, undated (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1389-1390)
  - Florence Arnheim, 1961-1975 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1392-1402)
  - Grant Arnold, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1404-1427)
  - Laura Arnold, 1954 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1429-1430)
  - Art and the Official Mind, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1432-1440)
  - Art Association of Newport, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Reel 5914, Frame 1442-1449)
  - Art Barn, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 13-28)
  - Art in Embassies Program, 1960-1973 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 30-81)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1944-1967 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 83-94)
  - Artists Alpine Holiday and Festival, Ouray, Colorado, 1962-1970 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 96-107)
  - Artists Equity, 1947-1978, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 109-279)
  - Artists For Victory, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 281-283)
  - Artists' Guild of Washington, 1942-1959, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 285-397)
  - Artist's Proof, undated (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 399)
  - Art League of Northern Virginia, 1962-1977 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 401-403)
  - Art Rental Gallery, 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 405-408)
  - Arts Club of Washington, 1927 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 410-411)
  - Art Students' League, 1932 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 413-415)
  - Winifred Ashby, 1947-1978 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 417-443)
  - Lila Oliver Asher, 1963-1976 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 445-478)
  - Associated American Artists, 1949-1975 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 480-486)
  - Association for Physical and Mental Rehabilitation, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 488-490)
  - Mignon D. Atchison, 1971 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 492-493)
  - Lee Atkyns, 1952 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 495-497)
  - Georges Auric, 1983 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 499)
  - Averett College, 1943-1961 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 501-512)
  - Cornelia F. Avery, 1949 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 514-515)
  - Ayer: N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc., 1946-1948 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 517-531)
  - Letitia B., 1970 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 533-534)
  - Norman B., 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 536-537)
  - Victor Babin and Vitya Vronsky, 1946-1986, (11 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 539-976)
  - Franz Bader, 1934-1988, (5 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5915, Frame 978-1195)
  - Franz Bader, 1934-1988, (4 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1197-1364)
  - Frank Baer, 1925 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1366-1369)
  - Laura N. Baerstein, 1954-1977 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1371-1385)
  - Jim Bailey, 1956 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1387-1388)
  - Russell Bailey, 1947-1954 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1390-1391)
  - Mrs. Baker, undated (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1393-1394)
  - Charles Baker, 1942-1967 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1396-1410)
  - Frances H. Baker, 1948 (Box 5, Reel 5915, Frame 1412)
  - Sarah Baker, 1950-1982 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 13-70)
  - George Balanchine, 1962-1983 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 72-77)
  - Richard Bales, 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 79)
  - Mary Wilson Ball, 1949-1969 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 81-128)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1948-1984 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 130-142)
  - Robert Barbee, 1973 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 144)
  - Djuna Barnes, 1982 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 146)
  - Wilfred "Bill" Barnes, 1954-1976 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 148-186)
  - Martin Barooshian, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 188-198)
  - Lana Barring, 1960 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 200)
  - Richmond Barth, 1935-1944, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 202-219)
  - Florence L. Barton, 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 221)
  - Mrs. Stanley Bate, undated (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 223-224)
  - Clair Batigne, 1975 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 226)
  - Adelia Bauer, 1913 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 228-230)
  - Anne Baum, 1958 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 232)
  - Bay Printmakers Society, 1955 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 234-239)
  - Clarke Beach, 1953-1968 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 241-275)
  - Dennis Beall, 1961 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 277-278)
  - Romare Bearden, 1972 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 280-281)
  - Helen and Katharine Beatty, 1938-1956 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 283-288)
  - Louise Bechtel, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 290-297)
  - Eleanor Bedell, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 299-300)
  - Jimmy Begaye, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 302-307)
  - Thomas Beggs, 1955-1968 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 309-310)
  - Mattie Bell, undated (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 312)
  - Robert Bell, 1977 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 314)
  - Liz Bellis, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 316-327)
  - Laura and Murray Belman, 1969 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 329-332)
  - Alfred Bendiner, 1957-1965 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 334-354)
  - William S. Benedict, 1980 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 356)
  - Laura Bent, 1932-1979 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 358-369)
  - William and Marjorie Flack Bent, 1944-1958 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 371-379)
  - Marilyn Benjamin, 1980 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 381-387)
  - Eugene Bennett, 1967-1982 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 389-406)
  - Deborah Benson, 1978-1986 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 408-412)
  - Rita-Romilly Benson, 1938 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 414-415)
  - Kaare J. Berg, 1978 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 417-418)
  - Dorothy and Jo Berger, 1932-1968 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 420-454)
  - Berkman Family, 1959 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 456)
  - Berner's Hotel, London, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 458-460)
  - Leonard Bernstein, 1959 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 462)
  - Ron Bernstein, undated (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 464)
  - Florence Berryman, 1953-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 466-477)
  - Sadie Bessell, 1956 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 479)
  - Margretta Best, 1945-1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 481-493)
  - Bethesda Art Gallery, 1975-1988 (4 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 495-647)
  - Bethesda-Chevy Chase Rescue Squad, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 649-650)
  - Elmira Bier, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 652-655)
  - Natalie Bigelow, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 657-661)
  - Mr. Biggs, 1978 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 663)
  - Jack Bilander, 1954-1974 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 665-670)
  - Bertha Birtwell, 1962 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 672)
  - Lorna Birtwell, 1931-1940 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 674-684)
  - Florence Bishop, 1945 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 686-688)
  - Mrs. Slavko N. Bjelajac, 1958 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 690)
  - Marjorie H. Black, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 692-694)
  - Morris Blackburn, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 696-699)
  - Peter Blanc, 1951-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 701-703)
  - Robert and Mildred Bliss, 1938-1964 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 715-734)
  - Marc Blitzstein, 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 736-737)
  - Carlos Blume, 1959 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 739)
  - Peter Blume, undated (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 741-742)
  - Joseph Blumenthal, 1944 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 744-749)
  - Carroll F. Boardman, 1946 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 751)
  - Belle Boas, 1944-1953 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 753-791)
  - Rose Bogdanoff, 1957 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 793)
  - T. E. Bolen, 1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 795-796)
  - Sara Bomberg, 1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 798)
  - Paul Bond, 1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 800-801)
  - Boosey & Hawks, 1974 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 803)
  - Albie Booth, 1959 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 805)
  - Lucrezia Bori, 1960 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 807)
  - Boston Museum Shop, 1950-1985 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 809-831)
  - Boston Printmakers, The, 1954-1973 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 833-886)
  - Boston Public Library Print Department, 1951-1982 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 888-923)
  - Jack Boul, 1957-1986 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 925-932)
  - Rudyerd Boulton and Louise Rehm, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 934-997)
  - Mortimer Bourne, 1948 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 999-1005)
  - Catherine Drinker Bowen, 1973 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1007)
  - A. Smith Bowman, 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1009)
  - Mary A. Boyd, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1011-1014)
  - William E. Boyle, 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1016-1019)
  - Lothar Brabanski, undated (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1021-1022)
  - Helen Bradfield, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1024-1033)
  - Lucrecia Quiroz Brady, 1965-1975 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1035-1047)
  - Laura M. Bragg, 1964-1978 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1049-1065)
  - Sarah Braverman, 1979 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1067)
  - Elizabeth "Libby" (Gove) and Wendell P. Brazeau, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1069-1108)
  - Alexandere Breckinridge, 1937 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1110-1117)
  - Adelyn Dohme Breeskin, 1936-1986 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1119-1149)
  - Edgar Breitenbach, 1966-1978 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1151-1165)
  - Henri Brenner, 1932 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1167-1175)
  - Brentano's, 1928 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1177)
  - Edwin H. "Herman" Bressler, 1927-1942, (4 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1179-1300)
  - Franklin N. Brewer, 1931-1948 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1302-1341)
  - Bentley Bridgewater, 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1343-1348)
  - Florence Briggs, 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1350)
  - British & Irish Railways, Inc., 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1352)
  - British Museum, 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1354-1355)
  - Emily R. Brittani, 1955 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1357-1358)
  - Harry A. Broad, 1944 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1360-1366)
  - Catherina "Kitty" Broches, 1982 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1368)
  - Judith K. Brodsky, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1376-1387)
  - Ann C. Brolin, 1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1389-1390)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1938-1955 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1392-1399)
  - Rev. George Brooks, 1954 (Box 5, Reel 5916, Frame 1401)
  - Don Brown, 1950-1968 (Box 6, Reel 5916, Frame 1404-1436)
  - Jean M. Brown, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Reel 5916, Frame 1438-1441)
  - Margaret Stow Bruce, 1948-1979 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 13-55)
  - Rev. Ernest Bruder, 1953-1976 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 57-58)
  - John Bryans, 1960-1980 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 60-78)
  - Henry H. Brylawski, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 80-82)
  - Andrew Bucci, 1949-1985, (5 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 84-189)
  - Harlan Buchalter, undated (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 191)
  - Carl Buchman, 1928-1929 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 193-196)
  - Jaime Buenaventura, 1968 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 198-199)
  - Remo and Florence Bufano, 1929-1954, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 201-246)
  - Dr. Dexter M. Bullard, 1958-1981 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 248-253)
  - Cecil Buller, 1948 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 255-261)
  - Bulletin of Art Therapy, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 263-269)
  - Isabel Burgess, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 271)
  - Marguerite Burgess, 1944-1984 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 273-287)
  - Don Burholz, 1948 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 289-290)
  - Martin David Burkenroad, 1933-1981, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 292-436)
  - Donald L. Burnham, 1961 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 438)
  - Roger M. Burnham, 1965 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 440)
  - John Burns, 1949 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 442-443)
  - Barbara Burton, 1958 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 445-446)
  - Harvey Bush, 1950s (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 448)
  - Anne Bushart, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 450-454)
  - Margaret Bussey, 1981 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 456-457)
  - Margaret Butcher, 1963 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 459-462)
  - A. J. Buttitta, 1933 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 464-467)
  - Robert Byrne, 1926-1963, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 469-588)
  - Ray C., 1978 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 590)
  - Paul Cadmus, 1942-1984 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 592-598)
  - William H. Calfee, 1942-1982 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 600-658)
  - California Society of Etchers/California Society of Printmakers, 1959-1973 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 660-696)
  - California Western University, 1960 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 698)
  - Sarah H. Callaham, 1960-1977 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 700-710)
  - John L. Cameron, 1983 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 712)
  - Jewett and Jeanne Campbell, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 714-728)
  - Marion Canby, 1932-1938 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 730-735)
  - Cannon's Seafood, Inc., 1981 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 737)
  - Canyon de Chelly National Monument, 1963 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 739)
  - Barbara Caples, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 741-759)
  - G. A. Cardwell, Jr., 1933-1934 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 761-763)
  - Carl Carmer, 1976 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 765)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1946-1978, (5 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 767-994)
  - Carolina Art Association (see also Gibbes Art Gallery), 1958-1985 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 996-1044)
  - Betts and Bob Carpenter, 1946-1952 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1046-1071)
  - Fitz Roy Carrington, 1929-1955 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1073-1087)
  - Ed Casarella, 1958 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1089-1090)
  - June Cary, 1955-1959 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1107)
  - James F. Casey, 1962 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1109)
  - Frank Cassidy, 1978 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1111)
  - Nico Castel, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1113-1114)
  - Federico and Hilda Castellon, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1116-1120)
  - Thelma M. Castle, 1976 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1121)
  - Catholic University of America, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1123-1125)
  - Thomas Catron, 1973 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1127)
  - Bennet Cerf, 1947 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1129)
  - Marian Chace, 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1131-1132)
  - Adelaide Chamberlain, 1928-1931 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1134-1141)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, 1948 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1143)
  - Helen and Bob Chambers, 1950-1975 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1145-1150)
  - Wally Chandler, 1958 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1152)
  - Rebecca Chang?, undated (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1154-1155)
  - Chaparral Indian Trading Company, 1963 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1157)
  - Dick Chapline, 1952 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1159)
  - Charleston, South Carolina, 1934-1986 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1161-1197)
  - G. Charlesworth, 1952 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1199-1203)
  - Leslie and Mary Tyler Cheek, undated (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1205-1206)
  - William Cheesman, 1948-1964 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1208-1210)
  - Chestnut Lodge Hospital, 1947-1986, (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1212-1325)
  - Chevy Chase Presbyterian Church, 1956 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1327-1328)
  - G. Alan Chidsey, 1939 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1330-1333)
  - Clifford Chieffo, 1967 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1335-1336)
  - Children's Art Gallery, Inc., 1942-1947 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1338-1401)
  - Walter Frank Choinski, 1960 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1403-1405)
  - William Christenberry, 1976 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1407-1409)
  - Christian Science Exhibit Halls, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Reel 5917, Frame 1411-1415)
  - Christian Science Exhibit Halls, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 13-62)
  - Clara B. Church, 1955 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 64-65)
  - Joanne Chutter, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 67-70)
  - Hortense and Nicolai Cikovsky, 1943-1962 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 72-83)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1956-1960 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 85-90)
  - Minna Citron, 1966-1976 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 92-116)
  - Jim Claiborne, 1936 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 118)
  - Clarendon Library, 1954 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 120-121)
  - Clarendon Trust Company, 1964 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 123)
  - Jill Clark, 1980 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 125)
  - Pat Clark, 1956 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 127-129)
  - Sidney E. Clark and Eleanor Clark, 1936-1975, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 131-229)
  - William S. Clark, 1943-1955 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 231-253)
  - John G. "Jack" Clarke, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 255-271)
  - Cyril Clemens, 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5918, Frame 273)
  - Cleveland Institute of Music Show, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 276-349)
  - Cleveland Institute of Music Show, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 351-386)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1938-1948 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 388-390)
  - Frederica Clucas, 1978 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 392-393)
  - Harold Clurman, 1980 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 395)
  - Christine Sadler Coe (Mrs. Richard Livingston Coe), 1957-1983 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 397-399)
  - Ila Coe, 1980 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 401-402)
  - C. S. Coen?, 1920? (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 404-409)
  - Karl F. Cohen, 1961 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 411-412)
  - Lydia Cohen, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 414-415)
  - Nathalie Colby, 1932-1934 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 417-420)
  - John Coleman, 1949 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 422)
  - H. Bacon Collamore, 1937-1972 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 424-491)
  - Collector's Corner Gallery, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 493-497)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc., 1957 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 499-515)
  - Arthur N. Collins, 1950 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 517)
  - Henry Collins, 1961 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 519)
  - Richard J. Collins, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 521-524)
  - S. Colsworth, 1964 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 526-527)
  - Padraic and Mary "Molly" Colum, 1930-1957 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 529-530)
  - Columbia Historical Society, 1986 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 532-537)
  - Columbia Museum of Art, 1952 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 539)
  - Eben F. Comins, 1926-1935 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 541-546)
  - Margaret F. Conard, 1955 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 548-549)
  - Etta Cone, 1945-1949 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 551-556)
  - Marc Connelly, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 558-559)
  - Connoisseurs, Ltd., 1960 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 561-562)
  - Robert G. Connolly, 1945 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 564)
  - Alida Conover, 1944-1981, (3 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 566-767)
  - Helen F. Conover, 1952-1954 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 769-775)
  - Cindy Conrad, 1975 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 777)
  - George Constant, 1948 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 779-780)
  - Contempo, 1933 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 782-790)
  - Grant Conway, 1976 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 792)
  - Helen Fetter Cook, 1925-1974, (4 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 794-931)
  - Helen Fetter Cook, 1925-1974 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 933-1018)
  - Hereward Lester Cooke, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1020-1028)
  - Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge, 1949-1953 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1030-1032)
  - Aaron Copland, 1928-1983, (3 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1034-1118)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1947-1977 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1120-1165)
  - Julia Cordley?, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1167-1168)
  - Katharine Cornell, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1170-1171)
  - Cornell University, 1956 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1173-1174)
  - Florence Corning, 1957 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1176-1180)
  - Cosmos Club, 1977 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1182-1186)
  - Emma Courlander, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1188-1205)
  - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1930-1931 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1207-1208)
  - Craddock & Barnard, 1968-1977 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1210-1227)
  - Alan Crane, 1959-1972 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1229-1239)
  - Priscilla Crane, 1929? (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1241-1243)
  - Clare Crawford, 1928 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1245-1249)
  - Grace A. Crawford, 1954 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1251-1253)
  - Nelson Antrim Crawford, 1927-1963 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1255-1300)
  - Dorothea Creager, 1954-1960 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1302-1312)
  - Noche Crist, 1962-1975 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1314-1344)
  - Helen M. Cromwell, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1346)
  - Jasper Cropsey, 1968 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1348-1349)
  - Anne Crosby, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1351-1352)
  - Caresse Crosby, 1970 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1354)
  - Bernice Cross, 1957-1982 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1356-1382)
  - Charles Crowder, undated (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1384)
  - John W. Crowe, 1962 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1386)
  - Jos Luis Cuevas, 1954-1963 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1388-1397)
  - Gaffer Cummings, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1399-1401)
  - Theodore Cuno, 1946-1958 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1403-1407)
  - Mrs. F. W. Curd, 1945 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1409-1410)
  - Cyril, 1964 (Box 7, Reel 5918, Frame 1412)
  - Joseph S. Czestochowski, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 13-51)
  - George D., 1958 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 53)
  - Edward Dahlberg, 1929-1977 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 55-56)
  - Dorothy Dalby, 1952-1980 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 58-86)
  - Harriet Damon, 1960 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 88-94)
  - Antoinette Darden, 1960 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 96-97)
  - Alexandra Darrow, 1951 (Box 7, Reel 5919, Frame 99-102)